Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 1967
  - Olearius, Adam, 1603-1671, The travels of Olearius in seventeenth-century Russia (2cc)., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Oliver, Peter, 1713-1791, Peter Oliver's Origin & progress of the American Rebellion a Tory view., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Payne, Stanley G, Politics and the military in modern Spain., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Poggi, Gianfranco, Catholic Action in Italy; the sociology of a sponsored organization (2cc)., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Prosser, Eleanor, Hamlet and revenge., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Robinson, John A. T, Exploration into God., 1967 (Box 3)
  - Staden, Heinrich von, 16th cent, The land and government of Muscovy; a sixteenth-century account (2cc)., 1967 (Box 4)
  - Stolz, Lois Meek, 1894-, Influences on parent behavior., 1967 (Box 4)
  - United States. Dept. of State, The China white paper, August 1949., 1967 (Box 4)
  - Van Slyke, Lyman P, Enemies and friends; the united front in Chinese Communist history (2cc)., 1967 (Box 4)
  - Zetterbaum, Marvin, Tocqueville and the problem of democracy., 1967 (Box 4)
- 1968
  - Alba, Víctor, Politics and the labor movement in Latin America., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Baker, Hugh D. R, A Chinese lineage village: Sheung Shui., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Barker, Roger G, Ecological psychology; concepts and methods for studying the environment of human behavior., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Chesneaux, Jean, The Chinese labor movement, 1919-1927., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralf, Essays in the theory of society., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Duberman, Martin B, Charles Francis Adams, 1807-1886., 1968 (Box 1)
  - Emery, Ashley F., ed, Proceedings of the 1968 Heat Transfer and Fluid Mechanics Institute, held at the University of Washington, Seattle, Washington, June 17, 18 1968. (Box 1)
  - Engels, Friedrich, 1820-1895, The condition of the working class in England., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Fagen, Richard R, Cubans in exile; disaffection and the revolution., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Frost, Richard H, The Mooney case., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Gamble, Sidney D, Ting Hsien; a north China rural community., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Gimbel, John, The American occupation of Germany; politics and the military, 1945-1949., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Haas, Ernst B, The uniting of Europe; political, social, and economic forces, 1950-1957., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hultén, Eric, 1894-, Flora of Alaska and neighboring territories; a manual of the vascular plants., 1968 (Box 3)
  - Jeffares, A. Norman, A commentary on the collected poems of W.B. Yeats., 1968 (Box 2)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1923-, Total positivity., 1968 (Box 3)
  - Korth, Eugene H, Spanish policy in colonial Chile; the struggle for social justice, 1535-1700., 1968 (Box 3)
  - Levenson, J. C. (Jacob Clavner), 1922-, The mind and the art of Henry Adams., 1968 (Box 3)
  - Madison, Bernice Q, Social welfare in the Soviet Union., 1968 (Box 3)
  - McCullough, Helen Craig, transl, Tales of Ise; lyrical episodes from tenth-century Japan. Ise monogatari. English.., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Meritt, Herbert Dean, 1904-, Some of the hardest glosses in Old English., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Miner, Earl Roy, An introduction to Japanese court poetry., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Packer, Herbert L., 1925-1972, The limits of the criminal sanction., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Radius, Walter Albrecht, 1910-, United States shipping in Transpacific trade, 1922-1938., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Reardon, Bernard M. G, Liberal Protestantism., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Ricketts, Edward Flanders, 1896-1948, Between Pacific tides; 4th ed., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Romero, José Luis, 1909-, A history of Argentine political thought., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Schorer, Mark, 1908-, Lawrence in the war years; with a check list of his correspondence in the Charlotte Ashley Felton Memorial Library of the Stanford University Libraries on the occasion of an exhibition in the Albert M. Bender Room, 30 October 1968. (Box 4)
  - Sharman, Lyon, 1872-1957, Sun Yat-sen; his life and its meaning; a critical biography., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Stegner, Wallace Earle, 1909-, Stanford short stories 1968. (Box 4)
  - Thompson, Virginia McLean, 1903-, Djibouti and the Horn of Africa., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Thornton, Michael John, Napoleon after Waterloo; England and the St. Helena decision., 1968 (Box 5)
  - United States. War Dept, The Chinese Communist movement; a report of the United States War Department, July 1945., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Vucinich, Wayne S., editor, The Peasant in nineteenth-century Russia., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Waley, Arthur, The Opium War through Chinese eyes., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Whiting, Allen Suess, 1926-, China crosses the Yalu; the decision to enter the Korean War., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Whiting, Allen Suess, 1926-, Soviet policies in China, 1917-1924., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Willis, F. Roy (Frank Roy), 1930-, France, Germany, and the new Europe, 1945-1967; Rev. and expanded ed., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Woolman, David S, Rebels in the Rif; Abd el Krim and the Rif Rebellion., 1968 (Box 5)
  - Xu, Zhuoyun, 1930-, Ancient China in transition: an analysis of social mobility, 722-222 B.C., 1968 (Box 5)
- 1969
  - Abernethy, David B, The political dilemma of popular education; an African case., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Alston, Patrick L, Education and the State in tsarist Russia., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Beckmann, George M, The Japanese Communist Party, 1922-1945., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Benson, Lyman David, 1909-, The native cacti of California., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Bitton, Davis, 1930-, The French nobility in crisis, 1560-1640., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Butow, Robert J. C. (Robert Joseph Charles), 1924-, Tojo and the Coming of the War., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Butwell, Richard A, U Nu of Burma., 1969 (Box 1)
  - Campenhausen, Hans, Freiherr von, 1903-, Ecclesiastical Authority and Spiritual Power in the Church of the First Three Centuries., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Campenhausen, Hans, Freiherr von, 1903-, The fathers of the Latin Church., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Clegg, P. Catherine, Hormones, cells, and organisms; the ns2:role of hormones in mammals., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Fagen, Richard R, The transformation of political culture in Cuba., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Fairbank, John King, 1907-, Trade and diplomacy on the China coast; the opening of the treaty ports 1842-1854., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Goody, Jack, Comparative studies in kinship., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Gordon, Michael R., 1939-, Conflict and consensus in Labour's foreign policy, 1914-1965., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Gregorian, Vartan, The emergence of modern Afghanistan; politics of reform and modernization, 1880-1946., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Gunther, Gerald, 1927-, John Marshall's defense of McCulloch v. Maryland., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Heath, O. V. S. (Oscar Victor Sayer), The physiological aspects of photosynthesis., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Heimbeck, Raeburne Seeley, Theology and meaning: a critique of metatheological scepticism., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Kaltenmark, Max, Lao Tzu and Taoism., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Keene, Donald, The Japanese discovery of Europe, 1720-1830; Rev. ed., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Legg, Keith R., 1935-, Politics in modern Greece., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving, 1883-1964, Values and imperatives; studies in ethics., 1969 (Box 3)
  - McFarland, Andrew S., 1940-, Power and leadership in pluralist systems., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Mendelowitz, Daniel M, Children are artists. An introduction to children's art for teachers and parents; 2nd ed., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Merryman, John Henry, The civil law tradition; an introduction to the legal systems of Western Europe and Latin America., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Munro, Donald J, The concept of man in early China., 1969 (Box 3)
  - Potash, Robert A., 1921-, The army & politics in Argentina., 1969 (Box 4)
  - Pyle, Kenneth B, The new generation in Meiji Japan; problems of cultural identity, 1885-1895., 1969 (Box 4)
  - Qu, Tongzu, Local government in China under the Ch'ing., 1969 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Gilbert Morgan, 1885-1959, Marine algae of the Monterey eninsula, California;2nd. ed., incorporating the 1966 Supplement by George J. Hollenberg and Isabella A. Abbott., 1969 (Box 4)
  - Strong, Edward K, Supplement for men's form T399 and women's form T398., 1969 (Box 4)
  - United States. Constitution, Your rugged constitution: how America's house of freedom is planned and built., 1969 (Box 4)
  - Wade, Rex A, The Russian search for peace, February-October 1917., 1969 (Box 4)
- 1970
  - Ch'ien, Tuan-shêng, The government and politics of China, 1912-1949., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Chubb, Basil, The government & politics of Ireland., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Dallin, Alexander, Political terror in communist systems., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Dollinger, Philippe, The German Hansa., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Freedman, Maurice, editor, Family and kinship in Chinese society., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Haas, Ernst B, Human rights and international action; the case of freedom of association., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Jeffares, A. Norman, The circus animals; essays on W. B. Yeats., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Chalmers, editor, Change in Communist systems., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Lerner, Warren, Karl Radek, the last internationalist., 1970 (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving, 1883-1964, Collected papers of Clarence Irving Lewis., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Pearson, Scott R, Petroleum and the Nigerian economy., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Pole, J. R. (Jack Richon), The Revolution in America, 1754-1788; documents and commentaries., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Powell, G. Bingham, Social fragmentation and political hostility; an Austrian case study., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Jackson K., 1929-, Old-age politics in California; from Richardson to Reagan., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Reardon, Bernard M. G, Roman Catholic Modernism., 1970 (Box 2)
  - Rocq, Margaret Miller, California local history; a bibliography and union list of library holdings., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Sarpkaya, Turgut, Proceedings of the 1970 heat transfer and fluid mechanics institute. (Box 3)
  - Seaver, Paul S, The Puritan lectureships; the politics of religious dissent, 1560-1662., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Sherwood, John M, Georges Mandel and the Third Republic., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Soustelle, Jacques, 1912-, Daily life of the Aztecs, on the eve of the Spanish conquest., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Stourzh, Gerald, Alexander Hamilton and the idea of republican government., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Taylor, James L. (James Lumpkin), 1892-, A Portuguese-English dictionary Rev., with corrections and additions by the author and Priscilla Clark Martin., 1970 (Box 3)
  - Vucinich, Alexander, 1914-, Science in Russian culture (2 cc)., 1970 (Box 4)
  - Wagner, Robert Harrison, United States policy toward Latin America; a study in domestic and international politics., 1970 (Box 4)
  - Waley, Arthur, Yuan Mei, 8th Century Chinese Poet., 1970 (Box 4)
  - White, James W, The Sokagakkai and mass society., 1970 (Box 4)
  - Wirth, John D, The politics of Brazilian development 1930-1954 (2 cc)., 1970 (Box 4)
- 1971
  - Bianco, Lucien, Origins of the Chinese Revolution 1915-1949., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Campbell, David P, Handbook for the strong vocational interest blank., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Cracraft, James, The church reform of Peter the Great., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Davis, John D, The interview as arena; strategies in standardized interviews and psychotherapy., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Ferguson, Charles Albert, 1921-, Language structure and language use; essays., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Gillis, John R, The Prussian bureaucracy in crisis, 1840-1860; origins of an administrative ethos., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Greenberg, Joseph Harold, 1915-, Language, culture, and communication., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Francis L. K., 1909-, Under the ancestors' shadow; kinship, personality, and social mobility in China., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Jansen, Marius B, Sakamoto Ry¯oma and the Meiji Restoration., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Allen W, Sharecroppers of the sertão; economics and dependence on a Brazilian plantation., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, G. Wesley, The Emergence of Black Politics in Senegal., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Josipovici, Gabriel, 1940-, The world and the book; a study of modern fiction., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Keen, A. Myra, Sea shells of tropical west America; marine mollusks from Baja California to Peru. 2nd edition., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Knowles, David, b. 1896, Thomas Becket., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Komunistická strana *Ceskoslovenska. Úst*rední v?bor. Komise pro vy*rizování stranick?ch rehabilitací, The Czechoslovak political trials, 1950-1954; the suppressed report of the Dubcek Government's commission of inquiry., 1971 (Box 2)
  - Lewis, John Wilson, editor, The City in Communist China., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Love, Joseph LeRoy, Rio Grande do Sul and Brazilian regionalism, 1882-1930., 1971 (Box 3)
  - McCullough, Helen Craig, transl, Yoshitsune: a fifteenth-century Japanese chronicle., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Prosser, Eleanor, Hamlet and revenge; 2d ed., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Rachewiltz, Igor de, Papal envoys to the great khans., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Schmitter, Philippe C, Interest conflict and political change in Brazil., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Tomsich, John, 1935-, A genteel endeavor; American culture and politics in the gilded age., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Wiggins, Ira L. (Ira Loren), 1899-, Flora of the Galápagos Islands., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Wilkie, Raymond, San Miguel: a Mexican collective ejido., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Frank Lee, 1941-, The French democratic Left, 1963-1969; toward a modern party system., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Zelnik, Reginald E, Labor and society in tsarist Russia; the factory workers of St. Petersburg, 1855-1870., 1971 (Box 4)
- 1972
  - Andrus, J. Russell, Trade, finance, and development in Pakistan., 1966 (Box 4)
  - Beasley, W. G. (William G.), 1919-, The Meiji restoration., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Boyle, John Hunter, China and Japan at war, 1937-1945; the politics of collaboration., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Cancian, Frank, Change and uncertainty in a peasant economy: the Maya corn farmers of Zinacantan., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Ch'ên, Jerome, 1919-, Yuan Shih-k'ai; 2d ed., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Chesneaux, Jean, editor, Popular movements and secret societies in China, 1840-1950., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Fagen, Richard R, Politics and privilege in a Mexican city., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Fishman, Joshua A, Language in sociocultural change., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Green, George D, Finance and economic development in the Old South; Louisiana banking, 1804-1861., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Gumperz, John Joseph, 1922-, Language in social groups., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Haugen, Einar Ingvald, 1906-, The ecology of language., 1972 (Box 4)
  - Ingram, James C, Economic change in Thailand, 1850-1970., 1971 (Box 4)
  - International Symposium on Psoriasis, Psoriasis: proceedings International Symposium on Psoriasis., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, Arthur Garfield, 1880-1954, A concise bibliography for students of English; 5th ed., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Lambert, Wallace E, Language, psychology, and culture., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Landis, Raymond B, Proceedings of the 1972 heat transfer and fluid mechanics institute. (Box 2)
  - Maccoby, Eleanor E., editor, The development of sex differences., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Midelfort, H. C. Erik, Witch hunting in southwestern Germany, 1562-1684; the social and intellectual foundations., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Orleans, Leo A, Every fifth child: the population of China., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Pasternak, Burton, Kinship & community in two Chinese villages., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Poggi, Gianfranco, Images of society; essays on the sociological theories of Tocqueville, Marx, and Durkheim., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Stein, Rolf Alfred, 1911-, Tibetan civilization., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Taylor, William B, Landlord and peasant in colonial Oaxaca., 1972 (Box 2)
  - Tien, Hung-mao, 1938-, Government and politics in Kuomintang China, 1927-1937., 1972 (Box 3)
  - Tobias, Henry Jack, The Jewish Bund in Russia from its origins to 1905., 1972 (Box 4)
  - Vucinich, Wayne S., editor, The Peasant in nineteenth-century Russia., 1968 (Box 4)
  - Willame, Jean-Claude, Patrimonialism and Political Change in the Congo., 1972 (Box 3)
  - Willmott, W. E., editor, Economic organization in Chinese society., 1972 (Box 3)
  - Wolf, Margery, Women and the family in rural Taiwan., 1972 (Box 3)
- 1973
  - Modern Chinese society; an analytical bibliography. Vol. 1-2., 1973 (Box 1)
  - Modern Chinese society; an analytical bibliography. Vol. 3., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Adelman, Irma, Economic growth and social equity in developing countries., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Ahern, Emily, The Cult of the Dead in a Chinese Village., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Bershader, Daniel and Wayland Griffith, editors, Recent developments in shock tube research; proceedings International Shock Tube Symposium., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Chace, William M, The political identities of Ezra Pound & T. S. Eliot., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Collier, Jane Fishburne, Law and social change in Zinacantan., 1973 (Box 2)
  - Dahl, Robert Alan, 1915-, Size and democracy., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Elvin, Mark, The Pattern of the Chinese Past., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Ervin-Tripp, Susan M., Language acquisition and communicative choice., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Fabrega, Horacio, Illness and Shaministic Curing in Zinacantan., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-, Blepharisma; the biology of a light-sensitive protozoan., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Girard, René, 1923-, Myth and ritual in Shakespeare: A midsummer night's dream., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Kadish, Mortimer R, Discretion to disobey; a study of lawful departures from legal rules., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Kruger, Paul and Carel Otte, editors, Geothermal energy; resources, production, stimulation., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Bradford A, Britain and the Sino-Japanese War, 1937-1939; a study in the dilemmas of British decline., 1973 (Box 3)
  - Okawa, Kazushi, 1908-, Japanese economic growth; trend acceleration in the twentieth century., 1973 (Box 4)
  - Rider, Frederick, The dialectic of selfhood in Montaigne., 1973 (Box 4)
  - Ronfeldt, David F, Atencingo; the politics of agrarian struggle in a Mexican ejido., 1973 (Box 4)
  - Webster, Brenda S, Yeats, a Psychoanalytic Study., 1973 (Box 4)
  - Williams, R. Hal, The Democratic Party and California Poliltics 1880-1896., 1973 (Box 4)
- 1974
  - Beaglehole, J. C, The Life of Captain James Cook., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Bowser, Frederick, The African Slave in Colonial Peru 1524-1650., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Butow, Robert J. C. (Robert Joseph Charles), 1924-, The John Doe Associates: backdoor diplomacy for peace, 1941., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Campbell, David P, SVIB, Strong vocational interest blank; manual for the Strong-Campbell interest inventory T325 (merged form)., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Cotler, Julio & Richard R. Fagen, editors, Latin America and the United States: the changing political realities., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Lorin R, Proceedings of the 1974 heat transfer and fluid mechanics institute. (Box 1)
  - Elvin, Mark and G. William Skinner, editors, The Chinese city between two worlds., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Ferejohn, John A, Pork barrel politics; rivers and harbors legislation, 1947-1968., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Lewis, John Wilson, 1930-, Peasant Rebellion and Communist Revolution in Asia., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Maccoby, Eleanor E, The Psychology of sex differences., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Meaker, Gerald H, The revolutionary left in Spain, 1914-1923., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Rosaldo, Michelle Zimbalist and Louise Lamphere, Woman, culture, and society., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Robert J, Ancestor Worship in Contemporary Japan., 1974 (Box 3)
  - Stanford University. Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford University, Report of the Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford., 1974 (Box 3)
  - Wolf, Arthur P., editor, Religion and ritual in Chinese society., 1974 (Box 3)
- 1975
  - Braroe, Niels W, Indian & White; self-image and interaction in a Canadian plains community., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Carré, Jean-Jacques, French economic growth., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Cornelius, Wayne A, Politics and the migrant poor in Mexico City., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Correll, Donovan S, Aquatic and wetland plants of southwestern United States. Vol 1 and 2 (2 copies each)., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralf, The new liberty: survival and justice in a changing world., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Natalie Zemon, 1928-, Society and culture in early modern France: eight essays., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Mark U., Luther and the false brethren., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Howe, Michael, Learning in infants and young children., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Jeffares, A. Norman, A commentary on the collected plays of W.B.Yeats., 1975 (Box 1)
  - Mathewson, Rufus W, The Positive hero in Russian literature., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Merryman, John Henry, editor, Stanford legal essays., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Marshall Lee, Bulgaria during the Second World War., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Nida, Eugene A, Language structure and translation., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Perkins, Dwight H, China's modern economy in historical perspective., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Tomasevich, Jozo, 1908-, The Chetniks., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Tugwell, Franklin, 1942-, The politics of oil in Venezuela., 1975 (Box 3)
  - Wolf, Margery and Roxane Witke, editors, Women in Chinese society., 1975 (Box 3)
- 1976
  - Abbott, Isabella A. and George J. Hollenberg, editors, Marine algae of California (2 cc.)., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Barton, John H. and Lawrence D. Weiler, editors, International arms control: issues and agreements., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Brazell, Karen, transl, Confessions of Lady Nijo., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bright, William, 1928-, Variation and change in language: essays., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Ch'i, Hsi-sheng, Warlord politics in china, 1916-1928., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Chao, Yuen Ren, 1892-, Aspects of Chinese sociolinguistics: essays., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Dean, Warren, Rio Claro; a Brazilian plnatation system., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Gimbel, John, The origins of the Marshall plan., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Hafkin, Nancy J. and Edna G. Bay, editors, Women in Africa: studies in social and economic change., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Kelly, Henry Ansgar, 1934-, The matrimonial trials of Henry VIII., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Kokov´t`sov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, graf, Out of my past: the memoirs of Count Kokovtsov, Russian Minister of finance, 1911-1914, Chairman of the Council of Ministers., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Mass, Jeffrey P, The Kamakura Bakufu: a study in documents., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Mayo, John K, Educational reform with television: the El Salvador experience., 1976 (Box 2)
  - McKillop, Allan A., ed, Proceedings of the 1976 heat transfer and fluid mechanics institute. (Box 2)
  - Montaigne, Michel de, 1533-1592, The complete essays of Montaigne., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Phillips, D. C. (Denis Charles), 1938-, Holistic thought in social science., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Potter, David Morris, Freedom and its limitations in American life (2 cc)., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Radwin, George E, Murex shells of the world: an illustrated guide to the Muricidae., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Regnery, Dorothy F, An enduring heritage: historic buildings of the San Francisco Peninsula., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Rocq, Margaret Miller, California local history: a bibliography and union list of library holdings: supplement to the second edition covering works published 1961 through 1970., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Sears, Robert R. (Robert Richardson), Patterns of child rearing., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Travis, Georgia, Chronic illness in children: its impact on child and family., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Ueda, Makoto, Modern Japanese writers and the nature of literature., 1976 (Box 3)
  - Weber, Eugen Joseph, 1925-, Peasants into Frenchmen: the modernization of rural France, 1870-1914., 1976 (Box 3)
- 1977
  - Allen, Paul Hamilton, 1911-1963, The rain forests of Golfo Dulce., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Atkinson, Dorothy [et. al.], editors, Women in Russia., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Blagden, Cyprian, The stationers' company: a history, 1403-1959., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Broom, Leonard, Opportunity and attainment in Australia., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Gann, Lewis H., 1924-, The rulers of German Africa, 1884-1914., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Given, James Buchanan, Society and homicide in thirteenth-century England., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Kirk, Ruth, Exploring Death Valley., 1977 (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865, Abraham Lincoln, a documentary portrait through his speeches and writings; ed. by Don E. Fehrenbacher., 1977 (Box 1)